Guide to the King County Labor Council Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- King County Labor Council records, 1889-1970; 1940-001; 18.26 cubic ft. 38 boxes
  - SERIES I: ADMINISTRATIVE RECORDS (Box-folder Boxes 1-24, 37, 38)
    - Subseries D: General Correspondence
      - Meeds, Lloyd, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 7/11)
      - Metal Polishers, Buffers, Platers, and Helpers International Union, Local #14, 1961-1964, 1968 (Box-folder 7/12)
      - Metal Trades Council of Seattle and Vicinity, 1960-1966 (Box-folder 7/13-14)
      - Musicians Association, Seattle, Local #76, 1960-1969 (Box-folder 7/15-17)
      - Re: Musician's Convention, 1962 (Box-folder 7/18)
      - National Conference of Christians and Jews. Washington Region, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 7/19)
      - National Council of Senior Citizens, 1964-1968 (Box-folder 7/20)
      - National Maritime Union of America, 1962-1963, 1967, 1969 (Box-folder 7/21)
      - Nile Shrine Circus, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 7/22)
      - Northwest Council for Economic Education, 1963-1967 (Box-folder 7/23)
      - Office and Professional Employees, Local #8, 1958 (Box-folder 7/24)
      - Office and Professional Employees, Local #8, 1958-1969 (Box-folder 8/1-2)
      - Office and Professional Employees, Local #349, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 8/3)
      - Offset Workers, Printing Pressmen, and Assistants' Union #39, 1960-1967 (Box-folder 8/4)
      - Operating Engineers, International, Local #286, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 8/5)
      - Operating Engineers, International Union, #302, 1960-1969 (Box-folder 8/6)
      - Operating Engineers, International Union, Local #303, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 8/7)
      - Operating Engineers, International Union, Local #609, 1961, 1969 (Box-folder 8/8)
      - Operative Plasterers and Cement Masons, International Association, Plasterer's Union Local #77, 1966 (Box-folder 8/9)
      - Operative Plasterers and Cement Masons, International Association, Cement Masons Local #528, 1960-1961, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 8/10)
      - Paint and Brush Makers Union #1094, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 8/11)
      - Painters, Decorators, and Paperhangers of America, Brotherhood, #5, 1959, 1963 (Box-folder 8/12)
      - Painters, Decorators, and Paperhangers of America, Brotherhood, #32, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 8/13)
      - Painters, Decorators, and Paperhangers of America, Local #188, 1959-1970 (Box-folder 8/14)
      - Painters, Decorators, and Paperhangers of America, Brotherhood, Local #300, 1961-1969 (Box-folder 8/15)
      - Painters, Decorators, and Paperhangers of America, Brotherhood, #1105, 1967 (Box-folder 8/16)
      - Pelly, Thomas, 1960-1969 (Box-folder 8/17-18)
      - Peoples National Bank of Washington, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 8/19)
      - Pharmacists and Retail Drug Store Employees Union #330, 1958-1969 (Box-folder 8/20-21)
      - Pile Drivers, Dock, Wharf, and Bridge Carpenters, and Divers, Local #2396, 1960 (Box-folder 8/22)
      - Plumbing and Pipe Fitters Union #32, 1964-1968 (Box-folder 8/23)
      - Police Officers, Renton, Local #953, 1959 (Box-folder 8/24)
      - Re: Political Material, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 8/25)
      - Portland Daily Reporter, 1963 (Box-folder 8/26)
      - Portrait, Commercial, and Photofinishers #23122, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 8/27)
      - Postal Clerks, United Federation of #28, 1959-1969 (Box-folder 8/28)
      - Postal Clerks, United Federation, Renton #3734, 1966 (Box-folder 9/1)
      - Printing Specialties and Paper Products Union #380, 1960-1969 (Box-folder 9/2)
      - Professional and Technical Engineers Association, Local #17, 1960-1969 (Box-folder 9/3)
      - Pulp, Sulfite, and Paper Mill Workers, Local #817, 1960, 1964 (Box-folder 9/4)
      - Radio Broadcast Technicians, Local Union 1264, 1967 (Box-folder 9/5)
      - Repeatermen and Toll Testboardmen #1011, 1960-1968 (Box-folder 9/6)
      - Restaurant Association of Washington State, 1960, 1963-1967 (Box-folder 9/7)
      - Retail Clerks, International Association, 1960-1967 (Box-folder 9/8)
      - Retail Clerks, International Association, Local #299, 1960-1967 (Box-folder 9/9)
      - Retail Clerks, International Association, Local #1207, 1959-1969 (Box-folder 9/10-12)
      - Retail Clerks, International Association, Local #1404, 1959-1967 (Box-folder 9/13-14)
      - Retail Clerks, International Association, Local #1421, 1960-1967 (Box-folder 9/15)
      - Retail Clerks, International Association, Local #1640, 1960-1968 (Box-folder 9/16)
      - Retail Food and Drug Clerks #1105, 1960-1969 (Box-folder 9/17)
      - Retail Store Employees Union #1001, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 9/18)
      - Roofers, United Slate, Tile and Composition, Damp, and Waterproof Workers' Association, Local #54, 1959, 1963 (Box-folder 9/19)
      - Sailors Union of the Pacific, 1961-1966 (Box-folder 9/20)
      - Re: Scanner, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 9/21)
      - Seafarers' International Union. Seattle, 1962-1968 (Box-folder 9/22)
      - Seattle. City Council, 1962-1967 (Box-folder 9/23-24)
      - Seattle. City Council. Equal Opportunities Seminar Committee, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 10/1)
      - Seattle. City Departments, 1961-1967 (Box-folder 10/2)
      - Seattle. Lighting Department. Electric Rates Committee, 1964, 1967 (Box-folder 10/3)
      - Seattle. Mayor (Gordon S. Clinton, J.D. Braman, Floyd C. Miller), 1960-1969 (Box-folder 10/4-5)
      - Seattle. Public Schools, 1954, 1957, 1960-1968 (Box-folder 10/6-8)
      - Seattle Area Industrial Council, 1959-1968 (Box-folder 10/9)
      - Seattle Center Stadium Site, Ad Hoc Committee, 1968 (Box-folder 10/10)
      - Seattle Committee on Alcoholism, 1964, 1966 (Box-folder 10/11)
      - Seattle Convention and Tourist Bureau, 1959-1968 (Box-folder 10/12)
      - Seattle Junior Programs, Incorporated, 1965, 1967 (Box-folder 10/13)
      - Seattle - King County Safety Council, 1960-1966 (Box-folder 10/14)
      - Seattle Newsboys' Union, Local #621, 1959-1969 (Box-folder 10/15)
      - Seattle Post-Intelligencer, 1961, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 10/16)
      - Seattle Symphony Orchestra, 1962-1969 (Box-folder 10/17)
      - Re: Seattle University Building Program, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 10/18)
      - Seattle Urban Renewal Enterprise, 1962-1966 (Box-folder 10/19)
      - Seattle Visitors Bureau, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 10/20)
      - Sheet Metal Workers, International Association #99, 1961-1964, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 10/21)
      - Sheet Metal Workers International Association #383, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 10/22)
      - Sign and Pictorial Painters Union #435, 1960-1969 (Box-folder 11/1)
      - State, County, and Municipal Employees #57, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 11/2)
      - State, County, and Municipal Employees American Federation Local #378, 1964 (Box-folder 11/3)
      - State, County, and Municipal Employees American Federation Miscellaneous Locals, 1961-1969 (Box-folder 11/4)
      - Steelworkers of America, United, Local #6, 1960, 1965 (Box-folder 11/5)
      - Steelworkers of America, United, Local #1208, 1960-1961, 1969 (Box-folder 11/6)
      - Steelworkers of America, United, Local #3112, 1958, 1966 (Box-folder 11/7)
      - Steelworkers of America, Miscellaneous Locals, 1958, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 11/8)
      - Stereotypers and Electrotypers Union, Seattle, Local #65, 1960-1969 (Box-folder 11/9)
      - Stinson, Bill, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 11/10)
      - Street, Electric Railway, and Motor Coach Employees of America, Amalgamated Association, Local #587, 1961-1969 (Box-folder 11/11)
        Name changed to Amalgamated Transit Union, 1965.
      - Street Pavers, Sewers, Watermain, and Tunnel Workers, #440, 1960-1963, 1969 (Box-folder 11/12)
      - Street Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America. Amalgamated Association, Local #1384, 1958-1960, 1966 (Box-folder 11/13)
      - Teachers, Federal Way Federation, #1738, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 11/14)
      - Teachers, Seattle Community College Federation, 1969 (Box-folder 11/15)
      - Teachers, Seattle Federation, 1961-1970 (Box-folder 11/16-17)
      - Teachers, Shoreline College Federation, #1950, 1969 (Box-folder 11/18)
      - Teamsters, International Brotherhood. Joint Council #28, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 11/19)
      - Teamsters Miscellaneous Locals, 1961-1962, 1969 (Box-folder 11/20)
      - Telegraph Workers, United Local #40, 1960-1970 (Box-folder 11/21)
      - Theatrical Federation of Seattle and Vicinity, 1960, 1962, 1968 (Box-folder 11/22)
      - Theatrical Press Agents and Managers, Association, Local #18032, 1962 (Box-folder 11/23)
      - Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators, International Alliance #F-21, 1960-1965 (Box-folder 11/24)
      - Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators, International Alliance, Local #15, 1960-1965 (Box-folder 11/25)
      - Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators, International Alliance, Local #154, 1961-1967 (Box-folder 11/26)
      - Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators, International Alliance, Local #175, 1967, 1969 (Box-folder 11/27)
      - Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators, International Alliance, Local #659, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 11/28)
      - Theatrical Wardrobe Attendants. Local #887, 1963-1969 (Box-folder 11/29)
      - Tollefson, Thor C., 1961-1964 (Box-folder 11/30)
      - Transport Service Employees, United, Local #903, 1963 (Box-folder 11/31)
      - Transport Workers Union of America, Local #506, 1963 (Box-folder 11/32)
      - Transport (Air) Workers' Union, Local #523, 1965 (Box-folder 11/33)
      - Turn Towards Peace, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 11/34)
      - Typographical Union, Seattle #202, 1960-1969 (Box-folder 11/35-36)
      - United Automobile-Aerospace-Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW) Local #232, undated (Box-folder 11/37)
      - U.S. Department of the Army, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 12/1)
      - U.S. President's Committee on Consumer Interests, 1968 (Box-folder 12/2)
      - U.S. Labor Department, 1961-1964, 1968 (Box-folder 12/3)
      - U.S. State Department. Educational and Cultural Affairs Bureau, 1963-1969 (Box-folder 12/4)
      - U.S. State Department, 1962-1969 (Box-folder 12/5)
      - U.S. Miscellaneous Departments, 1960-1968 (Box-folder 12/6)
      - University of Washington, 1960-1969 (Box-folder 12/7-8)
      - Upholsterers, International Union, Local #6, 1961-1969 (Box-folder 12/9)
      - Urban League [National] (leap program), 1967 (Box-folder 12/10)
      - Urban League. Seattle, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 12/11)
      - Valley Publishing Company, 1962 (Box-folder 12/12)
      - Waiters' Union, Local #239, 1960-1969 (Box-folder 12/13)
      - Waitresses' Union, Local #240, 1959-1969 (Box-folder 12/14)
      - Washington. Commerce and Economic Development Department, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 12/15)
      - Washington. Governor (Albert D. Rosellini, Daniel J. Evans), 1963-1968 (Box-folder 12/16)
      - Washington. Governor. Labor Advisory Council, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 12/17)
      - Washington. Labor and Industries, 1963-1967 (Box-folder 12/18)
      - Washington. Legislature. Interim Committee on Education, 1960, 1964 (Box-folder 12/19)
      - Washington. Public Assistance Department, 1960-1968 (Box-folder 12/20-22)
      - Washington. State Miscellaneous Departments, 1961-1966 (Box-folder 12/23)
      - Washington Federation of State Employees #976, 1959-1969 (Box-folder 13/1)
      - Web Pressmen's Union. Local #26, 1960-1969 (Box-folder 13/2)
      - Western Washington Fair, 1960-1967 (Box-folder 13/3)
      - Westland, Jack, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 13/4)
      - Window Cleaners Union, Local #23, 1961-1969 (Box-folder 13/5)
      - Women's City Club of Seattle, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 13/6)
      - Wood, Wire, and Metal Lathers International Union, Local #104, 1968 (Box-folder 13/7)
      - Woodworkers of America, International #3-26, 1963-1969 (Box-folder 13/8)
      - Young Women's Christian Association. Seattle, 1960-1968 (Box-folder 13/9)
      - A-R Miscellaneous, 1955, 1958-1969 (Box-folder 13/10-25)
      - S-Z Miscellaneous, 1959-1970 (Box-folder 14/1-7)
    - Subseries E: Subject Series
      - American Arbitration Association, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 14/8)
      - Apprenticeship Programs, 1962, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 14/9)
      - Banquet, 1962 (Box-folder 14/10)
      - Business - Education Day Program Schedule, 1959, 1963-1967 (Box-folder 14/11)
      - Charges Against Delegates, 1937, 1939 (Box-folder 14/12)
      - Civil Rights, 1963-1964, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 14/13)
      - Committee for Voluntary Unionism, 1967 (Box-folder 14/14)
      - Credentials, 1958, 1964 (Box-folder 14/15)
      - Education, 1959 (Box-folder 14/16)
      - Election Data, 1952-191957 (Box-folder 14/17)
      - Floating Ship Information, 1962 (Box-folder 15/1)
      - Forward Thrust, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 15/2)
      - Initiative #245, 1968 (Box-folder 15/3)
      - Labor Center, undated (Box-folder 15/4)
      - Labor Day, 1966 (Box-folder 15/5)
      - Labor Education Day (including photographs), 1954 (Box-folder 15/6-7)
      - Labor News (Miscellaneous), 1968-1969 (Box-folder 15/8)
      - "Labor Week", 1961-1966 (Box-folder 15/9)
      - Opera (Seattle), 1964 (Box-folder 15/10)
      - Political Information, 1952 (Box-folder 15/11)
      - Radio and Television Editorials, 1967 (Box-folder 15/12)
      - Registration Drive Clerks, 1968 (Box-folder 15/13)
      - Rossellini, Albert D., 1962 (Box-folder 15/14-15)
      - Rule 23, undated (Box-folder 15/16)
      - Seadrunar (Seattle Drug and Narcotics Center, Inc.), undated (Box-folder 15/17)
      - Seattle. Model City Program, 1968 (Box-folder 15/18)
      - Seattle General Strike, 1919 (Box-folder 15/19)
        - "Strike Bulletin" Central Labor Council, King County, Feb. 7, 1919
        - "The Seattle General Strike" Issued by the History Committee of the General Strike Committee
        - "Minutes of Meetings" of the General Strike Committee and its Executive Committee, Feb. 2-6, 1919
      - Seattle Leadership Council, 1961 (Box-folder 15/20)
      - Seattle Union Record Controversy, 1921-1925 (Box-folder 15/21)
      - "Seavillage", 1961 (Box-folder 15/22)
      - Self-Improvement Group, 1963 (Box-folder 15/23)
      - Seminars, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 15/24)
      - Senior Citizens, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 15/25)
      - Soos Creek - Zoning, 1969 (Box-folder 15/26)
      - Strikebreakers Ordinance - Typographical, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 15/27)
      - Trials, 1942, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 16/1)
      - Trials, Communist, 1925-1929 (Box-folder 16/2-3)
      - V.O.T.E.R. Committee, King County (Volunteer Organization To Encourage Registration), 1968 (Box-folder 16/4)
      - Washington. Department of Labor and Industry, 1959-1962 (Box-folder 16/5-6)
      - Washington. Legislature, 1961-1964, 1968 (Box-folder 16/7-11)
      - Washington State Federation of Labor Convention, 1962 (Box-folder 16/12-15)
      - Western Shipbuilding Association, 1962 (Box-folder 16/16-17)
    - Subseries F: Minutes, 1915-1927 (Box 17)
    - Subseries G: Minutes, 1928-1947 (Box 18)
    - Subseries H: Minutes, 1946-1962 (Box-folder 19/1-7)
    - Subseries I: Minutes, 1963-1970 (Box-folder 20/1-8)
    - Subseries J: Reports
      - Delegates, 1949-1967 (Box-folder 21/1-2)
      - Per Capita, 1957-1959 (Box-folder 21/3)
    - Subseries K: Conferences and Conventions - Washington State Federation of Labor, 1957-1961 (Box-folder 21/4-5)
    - Subseries L: Membership Records, 1962 (Box-folder 21/6)
    - Subseries M: Newsletters - The American Federalist, 1969 (Box-folder 21/7)
    - Subseries N: Bulletin - Associated Industries of Seattle, 1931 (Box-folder 21/8)
    - Subseries O: Press Releases, 1961, 1964 (Box-folder 21/9)
    - Subseries P: Resolutions
      - Condolence, 1948-1968 (Box-folder 21/10)
      - Miscellaneous, 1949-1968 (Box-folder 21/11)
    - Subseries Q: Agreements - Miscellaneous, 1937-1942 (Box-folder 21/12)
    - Subseries R: Case Files - News Boys Union, 1942 (Box-folder 21/13)
    - Subseries S: Petitions, 1967 (Box-folder 21/14)
    - Subseries T: Certificates and Memorabilia, 1952-1956 (Box-folder 21/15)
    - Subseries U: Photographs, 1941, 1958 (Box-folder 22/1-9)
    - Subseries V: Clippings, 1937-1941, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 22/10)
    - Subseries W: Ephemera
      - AFL-CIO, undated (Box-folder 22/11)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box-folder 22/12)
    - Subseries X: Financial Records, 1950-1960 (Box-folder 22/13-14)
    - Subseries Y: Roll Call Books, 1920-1964 (Box 23)
    - Subseries Z: Membership and Per Capita Tax Record, 1889-1892, 1907-1925 (Box 23)
    - Subseries AA: Membership and Per Capita Tax Record, 1926-1962 (Box 24)
    - Subseries BB: Cash Books, 1910-1919 (Box 24)
    - Subseries CC: Cash Books, 1926-1938 (Box:oversize 37)
    - Subseries DD: Cash Books, 1938-1950 (Box:oversize 38)
  - SERIES II: COMMITTEES AND BOARD RECORDS
    - Subseries A: King County Labor Council, Community Services Committee, 1960-1967 (Box-folder 25/17-18)
    - Subseries B: King County Labor Council, AFL-CIO Merger Committee, 1957 (Box-folder 25/1-3)
    - Subseries C: King County Labor Council, Committee to Defeat Initiative #198
      - Outgoing Letters - Form Letters to Clubs, Unions, Etc., 1956 (Box-folder 25/4)
      - General Correspondence
        - Seminar Correspondence, 1956 (Box-folder 25/5)
        - Miscellaneous, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 25/6)
      - Minutes
        - Seattle Central Labor Council's Committee to Oppose Initiative #198, 1956 (Box-folder 25/7)
        - United Labor Advisory Committee Against Initiative #198, 1956 (Box-folder 25/8)
      - Financial Records, 1956 (Box-folder 25/9)
      - Clippings, 1956 (Box-folder 25/10)
      - Ephemera, 1954 (Box-folder 25/11-12)
      - Resolutions, 1954 (Box-folder 25/13)
      - Press Release, undated (Box-folder 25/14)
      - Subject Series
        - Initiative 198 (PRO), 1956 (Box-folder 25/15)
        - Radio and T.V. Advertising, 1956 (Box-folder 25/16)
    - Subseries D: King County Labor Council, Constitution and By-Laws Committee, 1957, 1959, 1964 (Box-folder 25/19)
    - Subseries E: King County Labor Council, Executive Board
      - Minutes and Agenda, 1906-1907 (Box-folder 25/20)
      - Minutes and Agenda, 1913-1947 (Box 26)
      - Minutes and Agenda, 1947-1954 (Box-folder 27/1-12)
      - Minutes and Agenda, 1958-1963 (Box-folder 28/1-12)
      - Minutes and Agenda, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 29/1-11)
      - Minutes and Agenda, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 30/1-3)
      - Statement, 1923 (Box-folder 30/4)
    - Subseries F: King County Labor Council, Finance Committee, 1917, 1950-1957 (Box-folder 30/5-6)
    - Subseries G: King County Labor Council, King County Area C.O.P.E. (Committee On Political Education)
      - General Correspondence
        - Miscellaneous, 1958-1968 (Box-folder 30/7)
        - C.O.P.E. National, 1965, 1967 (Box-folder 30/8)
      - Minutes, 1958 (Box-folder 30/9)
      - Reports, 1958 (Box-folder 30/10)
      - Roll Call Book, undated (Box-folder 30/10)
      - News Releases, 1968 (Box-folder 30/11)
      - Clippings, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 30/12)
      - Financial Records, 1959-1960, 1964 (Box-folder 30/13)
      - Subject Series
        - Matching Funds, 1968 (Box-folder 30/14)
    - Subseries H: King County Labor Council, Labor Management - Automation and Unemployment Committee, 1966 (Box-folder 31/1)
    - Subseries I: King County Labor Council, Organizing Committee, 1964 (Box-folder 31/2)
    - Subseries J: King County Labor Council, Public Relations Committee, 1959-1966 (Box-folder 31/3-5)
    - Subseries K: King County Labor Council, Renton Division, 1959-1969 (Box-folder 31/6-7)
    - Subseries L: King County Labor Council, Seattle Union Card and Label Council (Including King County Union Card and Label Council) Trustees Board, 1958-1969 (Box-folder 31/8-9)
      - General Correspondence, 1958-1961 (Box-folder 31/10)
      - Minutes, 1958-1963 (Box-folder 31/11-12)
      - Memoranda, 1958 (Box-folder 32/1)
      - Reports
        - Trustees Board, 1957-1960 (Box-folder 32/2)
        - Monthly, 1958-1963 (Box-folder 32/3)
        - Financial, 1961 (Box-folder 32/4)
        - Secretary, 1958 (Box-folder 32/5)
      - Financial Records, 1957-1963 (Box-folder 32/6)
      - Finance Committee, 1958 (Box-folder 32/7)
      - Subject Series
        - Labor News, 1958-1965 (Box-folder 32/8-9)
        - Labor Press Publishing Company, 1950, 1960 (Box-folder 32/10)
  - SERIES III: WESTERN CENTRAL LABOR UNION
    - Subseries A: Minutes, 1891-1895, 1898-1905 (Box 35)
    - Subseries B: Cash Books, 1892-1902 (Box 35)
    - Subseries C: Cash Books, 1898-1912, 1917-1919 (Box 36)
    - Subseries D: Roll Call Books, 1901-1905, 1909-1914 (Box 36)
  - SERIES IV: OTHER LABOR ORGANIZATIONS
    - Subseries A: Domestic Workers Union #15836 (Box 36)
      - Minutes, 1917 (Box 36)
    - Subseries B: Seattle American Publishing Company (Box 36)
      - General Correspondence, 1907 (Box 36)
      - Record Book, 1907 (Box 36)
    - Subseries C: Seattle Labor Temple Association, 1942-1969 (Box-folder 32/11)
    - Subseries D: United Labor Advisory Committee Against Initiative 202, 1958 (Box-folder 32/12-26)
      - Incoming Letters - From Employers, 1958 (Box-folder 32/12)
      - Outgoing Letters, 1958 (Box-folder 32/13)
      - General Correspondence
        - Committee Against So - Called "Right-To-Work" Initiative #202, 1958 (Box-folder 32/14)
        - Luncheon Rally, 1958 (Box-folder 32/15-16)
      - Minutes
        - Committee Against Initiative 202, 1958 (Box-folder 32/17)
        - United Labor Advisory Committee Against Initiative 202, 1958 (Box-folder 32/18)
      - Newsletters, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 32/19)
      - Resolutions, 1958 (Box-folder 32/20)
      - Financial Records, 1958 (Box-folder 32/21)
      - Subject Series
        - Right-To-Work, 1955-1958 (Box-folder 32/22)
        - Committee for Initiative 202, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 32/23)
      - Ephemera, 1958 (Box-folder 32/24)
      - Clippings, 1958, 1960 (Box-folder 32/25-26)
    - Subseries E: Washington State Labor Council. Miscellaneous Trades Section, 1959-1968 (Box-folder 33/1-2)
    - Subseries F: Washington State Labor News, 1950-1968 (Box-folder 33/3-4)
  - Series V: Other Organizations
    - Subseries A: Capital Improvement Committee, 1960 (Box-folder 33/5)
    - Subseries B: Four Freedoms House of Seattle, 1961-1968 (Box-folder 33/6-7)
    - Subseries C: Greater Seattle, Inc. Board Of Directors, 1960-1968 (Box-folder 33/8-9)
    - Subseries D: Job Corps Committee - Seattle United, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 33/10)
    - Subseries E: John F. Kennedy Library Committee, 1964 (Box-folder 33/11)
    - Subseries F: Pioneer Industries, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 33/12)
    - Tallmadge Hamilton House for Senior Citizens, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 33/13)
    - United Good Neighbors of Seattle and King County, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 33/14)
    - United Good Neighbors of Seattle and King County, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 34/1-2)
    - Washington. Governor's Advisory Committee on Salaries, 1962-1968 (Box-folder 34/3-6)
    - Washington. Advisory Committee on School District Organization, 1964 (Box-folder 34/7)
    - Washington Association for Mental Health. Steering Committee, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 34/8)
    - Doyle, Charles W., 1933-1957 (Box-folder 34/9-10)
    - Merritt, Dick, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 34/11)
- King County Labor Council records, 1970-2003; 1990-2000; 1940-002; 20.00 cubic ft. 20 boxes
  Accession 1940-002 is divided into four series: Administrative Records, Correspondence with Affiliated Unions, Subject Series, and the Committee on Political Education.